[{
    "theme": "üåç Aprender idiomas",
    "langread": "es",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "What languages do you speak?",
            "answers": ["¬øQu√© idiomas hablas?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'to speak'?",
            "answers": ["hablar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'tourism'?",
            "answers": ["turismo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'school'?",
            "answers": ["colegio"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'high school'?",
            "answers": ["instituto"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'mandatory'?",
            "answers": ["obligatorio"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'of course'?",
            "answers": ["claro que s√≠"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am Spanish'?",
            "answers": ["yo soy espa√±ol"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'so' (as in 'so I did it')?",
            "answers": ["as√≠ que"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'important'?",
            "answers": ["importante"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'particularly'?",
            "answers": ["particularmente"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Did you study?'",
            "answers": ["¬øEstudiaste?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'to study'?",
            "answers": ["estudiar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'At what age?'",
            "answers": ["¬øA qu√© edad?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'It begins'?",
            "answers": ["Se empieza"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'When I was little'?",
            "answers": ["Cuando yo era peque√±o"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'before'?",
            "answers": ["antes"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'at eight years old'?",
            "answers": ["con ocho a√±os"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'to understand each other'?",
            "answers": ["entendernos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'furthermore' or 'besides'?",
            "answers": ["adem√°s"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'he/she came'?",
            "answers": ["vino"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'especially'?",
            "answers": ["especialmente"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Arabic'?",
            "answers": ["√°rabe"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Russian'?",
            "answers": ["ruso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'French'?",
            "answers": ["franc√©s"]
        }
    ]
}]